[

](https://openinventionnetwork.com/)

* About OIN

* Our Members

* Industries

    * * 
        
    * * 

* Media

* OIN Resources

* Linux System
    
    * * [OIN License  
            Agreement](https://openinventionnetwork.com/joining-oin/join-now/license-agreement/)
        * [The OIN License Agreement agreement states the rights and obligations of all parties, including each OIN community member and OIN.](#)
        
    * * [Linux System Definition  
            & Components](https://openinventionnetwork.com/linux-system/)
        * [The definition of the Linux System relevant to the OIN license agreement is described on this page and associated tables.](#)
        
    * * [Linux System Definition  
            Nominations](https://openinventionnetwork.com/media/linux-system-nominations/)
        * [This guide is intended for nominators of new packages for inclusion in the OIN Linux System definition.](#)

Search for: 

Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Policy[oin-admin](https://openinventionnetwork.com/author/oin-admin/ "Posts by oin-admin")2024-01-17T21:23:38-05:00

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Open Invention Network LLC (“OIN”) and our website [openinventionnetwork.com](http://openinventionnetwork.com/). This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
==========================================================================================================================================================================================================================================================================================

* What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
* What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
* The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
* How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We only collect information that you voluntarily give us via our website forms or via email or other direct contact from you.  
We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill our obligations to you under the OIN license agreement.

If you opt in to our mailing list, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about news, conferences, and other matters such as changes to this privacy policy.

### Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via email at [info@openinventionnetwork.com](mailto:info@openinventionnetwork.com):

* See what data we have about you, if any.
* Change/correct any data we have about you.
* Have us delete any data we have about you.
* Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

### Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit information via our electronic signature service, your information is protected both online and offline.

In our electronic signature service form, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only parties who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, licensing representatives and administrative officers for legal notices) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

### Electronic Signature and Related Forms

It is not required that organizations join the OIN community via our online electronic signature service, as organizations may mail in signed hardcopies of the OIN license agreement.  However, many organizations opt to do so for convenience.  To do so, a user at the organization must first complete online forms.  During the filling of these forms, a user is required to give certain information (such as name, email address, and title). Our electronic signature service also stamps your signed OIN license agreement with your IP address.  This information is used to verify the user’s identity and provide legal notices to your organization as required by the OIN license agreement.

### Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email at [info@openinventionnetwork.com](mailto:info@openinventionnetwork.com).**

Welcome to our Newest Members!

Testimonials

> Google has been a proud member of OIN since joining the community in 2007. Linux and adjacent open source software power the cloud-based services of today and tomorrow. Throughout, OIN has been there to ensure that open source remains safe for users, consumers, and developers alike to consume and upon which to build.

Chris DiBonaDirector of Open SourceGoogle

> As a global solutions provider that grows with customers and society through the highest level of trust, SMFG is committed to creating businesses that transcend the boundaries of finance and resolving issues. In order to further promote this effort and quickly deliver high added-value services to our customers and society, SMFG believes that the utilization of open source software will be essential. Also, in promoting OSS utilization, SMFG believes that measures to protect intellectual property … [Read more](https://173.230.129.118/testimonial/smfg/ "Complete testimonial by Sumitomo Mitsui Financial Group")

Sumitomo Mitsui Financial Group

> Open Source technologies, especially Embedded Linux, have enabled the rapid development of intelligent products that can be found throughout the infrastructure of homes. LIXIL’s participation in the OIN community shows our consistent commitment to open source innovation.  

Yugo KanazawaChief Digital OfficerLIXIL

> Foxconn continuously looks for ways to integrate advances into the design and manufacturing of smart consumer electronics, cloud and networking equipment, computing devices and components, among others. We are pleased to join the Open Invention Network and support its role in protecting open source.

Mick LimDirector, Foxconn IP Affairs Division

> With the Industrial Internet of Things (IIOT) reshaping what is possible in industrial settings — improving productivity, enhancing operational efficiency and increasing customer choice — we view Linux and other open source projects as key enablers in the IIOT. The success of the IIOT is predicated on the ability to connect and manage widely distributed sensors and devices across numerous vertical industries and compute the data effectively on an industrial scale.  

Peter KohlschmidtCTOMoxa

> Through our information platforms, people can be more creative and enrich their lives through deeper communications with their friends and family. We view Linux and adjacent open source software as key elements for our business. ByteDance’s participation in the OIN community shows our consistent commitment to shared innovation. We will continue to support it with patent non-aggression in core Linux and other important OSS technologies.  

Lynn WuChief IP CounselByteDance

> Global adoption of Linux and other open source technologies is an irreversible trend. For the last 15 years, they have transformed almost every industry. By sharing innovation, Linux and open source capabilities have soared, application interoperability is unprecedented, connectivity is virtually everywhere, while business and consumer productivity are at all-time highs. By blocking patent aggression in open source, OIN has enabled safer investments in product development and helped to enable th… [Read more](https://173.230.129.118/testimonial/nec-and-necam/ "Complete testimonial by Hirotake Konda - GM, IP Management Division & Department Manager, NEC // Jackson Chen - Senior Associate General Counsel, NCAM")

Hirotake Konda - GM, IP Management Division & Department Manager, NEC // Jackson Chen - Senior Associate General Counsel, NCAM

> _We are incredibly focused on pleasing our customers. One of the most effective ways to do that is to develop the systems and technologies that enable our customers to innovate. Building and leveraging open technologies enables businesses to more easily integrate their solutions — while empowering them to focus more of their resources in the powerful, distinguishing technologies that customers pursue. We are pleased to be part of the OIN community protecting open projects that encourage innovat… [Read more](https://173.230.129.118/testimonial/tokyo-electron-device/ "Complete testimonial by Kazuki Shinoda")_

Kazuki ShinodaSVP, Tokyo Electron Device, Ltd.

> This move (regarding Huawei’s OIN membership demonstrates that joining OIN has become a no-brainer for any product company. Setting aside the patent trolls, who would never have an incentive to join, no one is asserting patents against Linux anymore. Waging a patent war against a popular open-source project like Linux is bad for business. Of course, the OIN definition of Linux is far broader than the kernel. Even so, the OIN pool protects the basic infrastructure of the web, and no serious pro… [Read more](https://173.230.129.118/testimonial/omelveny-myers/ "Complete testimonial by Heather Meeker")

Heather MeekerPartnerO'Melveny & Myers

> As a global leader in open source, SUSE enables innovation from the largest data centers in the world to cloud environments, and our technology is embedded in every day devices like cars, points of sale and MRIs. Open source infrastructure is the power behind the cloud and digital transformation, and our customers rely on us for mission critical business outcomes and for innovation. As a leader in bringing open source solutions to enterprises, including enterprise Linux, we see firsthand why … [Read more](https://173.230.129.118/testimonial/thomas-di-giacomo-suse/ "Complete testimonial by Thomas Di Giacomo")

Thomas Di GiacomoPresident of Engineering & InnovationSUSE

[

](https://openinventionnetwork.com/)

Don’t miss out on Open Source industry news, events and more! Our **INSIDER eNewsletter** is sent bi-monthly and covers all things Open Source.

"\*" indicates required fields

Your Name\*

Email\*

Phone

This field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.

#### For our members

#### Industry Resources

#### Company

#### INFORMATION

Copyright © 2024 Open Invention Network | All Rights Reserved.
